New York
Hyun Bin
Yoo Hae-jin
Lim Yoona
Daniel Henney / Jin Seon-gyu
Director Lee Seok-hoon
You lost it all by being greedy.
Don't kill me...
Do you love money that much?
Please!
Then let's see if this
money can save you.
Please...
You Mother...
FBI! Hands up!
Damn.
It is a nice car.
Always wanted one of these.
Now get out.
Dammit, Jack! Are you out of your mind?
Mobilizing SWAT
without clearing it first?
What the heck were you thinking?
I got a tip,
I had to act.
- A tip?
- Yeah.
From who?
I got an e-mail,
I don't know who it is from.
Jesus, Jack, you are killing me.
Hey, it worked out.
Well...
Maybe congratulations are in order.
You have been after this
guy, what, a year now?
Why don't you take that vacation
you have been putting off?
No, no, there is no time for that,
we have to keep digging.
Follow the money,
find the sales network,
this guy could get a life sentence.
- Life?
- Yeah.
More like a firing squad.
Well, it is not North Korea.
Not yet.
Lim Cheol-ryung, funny seeing you here.
You abandoned the party
and became a drug peddler?
Aren't you ashamed
to see your comrades?
I heard your woman died
in front of your eyes.
What were you doing then?
That is what I call shameful.
Who is trying to steal my show, huh?
Is it you?
I am sorry, he just barged in.
As per the agreement with the U.S.,
he will be extradited to North Korea.
We appreciate your cooperation.
What the hell is this?
With all the waving
in my face?
You are interfering
with diplomatic delegation
affairs of North Korea.
All right, tough guy.
- Jack!
- I am ready now.
What the hell are you doing?
I told you our orders came straight
from the State Department.
You do know that we are in
the process of establishing
diplomatic relations with
the North Koreans, right?
You start the war right now,
- we can start right here.
- Okay, all right!
These men are our responsibility
until we get them on a plane,
so why don't you
continue this little dance
on the way to the airport.
Now!
All right.
Thank you, captain.
With the $100 you gave me yesterday,
I bought gifts for my family.
$100?
I thought I gave you $10.
I think it got switched, give it back.
Oh dear, I spent it all...
Did you prank me again?
Come on, captain.
I bought a few of these for my wife,
please take one with you.
No need.
I got no one to give it to.
Captain, enough time has passed.
And so many young women
desire your attention.
If I was born with that face,
I would not live like this.
Jack!
No!
Back, back, back!
Untie me.
Hey!
Cover me!
- Comrade!
- Damn it!
Let's go!
We should go.
Confidential Assignment 2:
International
Seoul
I am Investigator Kim
of the Prosecution Office.
Is this Ms. Kim Mi-young?
Your account is being used
for illegal transactions...
Your private information got leaked.
Please do not be alarmed.
Money in your account is in danger...
Hello, madame!
I am Jung-wook's friend, Sang-hoon.
- He got drunk...
- And got into a fight...
So he is at the police station.
- Mom?
- Hello? Hel...
Dammit!
Listen here, can't you
switch up the script?
No one gets deceived
because we are using the same crap!
I can't do this anymore.
Stupid idiot!
It is your damn acting,
stop blaming the script!
As you can see,
we are a typical telemarketing firm.
I am not sure if it is to your liking.
Telemarketing is all
about emotional labor.
But collection only deals
with getting the money.
You will get a 1% commission
from your collection.
1% is way too damn small.
If I get caught by the cops,
I am the only one screwed.
It sounds like you got some experience.
I worked in the Philippines for a year,
and a 2-year stint in Yanbian...
It would help if you had said so.
Can you write scripts too?
Well, people said
I should be getting a Pulitzer.
If you pay me $5,000 per gig,
I can write a killer episode.
What is that for?
Isn't that a camera?
You got an eagle eye.
I am actually a YouTuber, you know,
vlog and stuff.
You are a cop!
Everyone, run!
Not another step.
You thought you could run?
- Man, that hurts.
- It is so crowded.
I am Det. Kang Jin-tae of Major Crimes,
scumbags.
Fake accounts, burner
phones, forged passports,
where did you get them? Answer me!
Who is the supplier?
Screw the supplier,
I am cold and hungry...
this is so messed up,
when is he coming?
Hey.
I hope you guys aren't
eating anything without me.
A bowl of hot noodles would be
heaven right now...
We are not some pricks.
How could you say that?
He sure can sniff it out,
he really is a cop.
Look, he is here.
$1,000 per.
How many do you need?
Look, even the holograms are perfect.
I am the only one in Asia
who can pull this off.
Where are you from?
Russia? Koreyskiy?
Is it that obvious?
I came to my grandfather's hometown
to make money,
and I live near Korea University.
So, how many?
Excuse me?
Good evening, gents.
Are you the car owner?
Great work, you two.
Cop, cop.
This car comes up
as an illegal vehicle.
I see, I am a cop, cop.
Sergei.
Sergei!
He looks similar to the sketch
of the serial kidnapper...
It is not like that!
I am Major Crimes, Major Crimes.
It is a major crime for sure!
You guys are so clueless.
- Don't move, please.
- Yeah, a major crime.
Look, I was right!
You used this to kidnap girls!
You pervert!
That is why you need fake passports!
- Fake passports?
- Fake passports!
- I am a cop! Cop!
- Don't move!
I am a Major Crimes detective!
I am undercover to get this prick!
Damn it!
He is running away, go after him!
You idiot! Stop right there!
Crazy idiot!
Stop the car, idiot!
You magnetic scum!
Get rid of the noodles!
Hey! Sesame Ramyun?
We did not eat.
Why is he hanging on the hood?
If he falls off, stop the car, okay?
Stay on the right!
Jin-tae is going to fall!
Stop!
Be careful!
Damn you!
Don't cry, it is okay.
Where is your mom?
Mom...
Are you okay?
That could have been bad.
You should have blocked him.
Detective.
Look, blood.
What? Why do I have blood...
How is that...
Hey, easy!
2 months later
Cyber Crime Investigation
So you bought a used phone
from someone online...
My head...
And the box contained
fried chicken containers and bones?
There was a plastic bag too,
so I opened it,
and there were some feces.
Feces?
So many lunatics...
How big was the feces, about this big?
This big.
Was it human poop?
So, on May 6th,
Banghak internet cafe,
you two got into a
two-way assault, right?
Then it is a simple assault.
Why is the Cyber Bureau handling
a simple assault case?
Who registered this case?
I did, sir.
Is a fight at an internet
cafe a cybercrime?
He beat someone with a keyboard...
Jeez...
If it was a bundle of cash,
then it would be a financial crime?
And a calculator
would be a digital crime?
Sorry, sir.
- Genius.
- Damn.
Pyongyang
Patriotic Martyrs' Cemetery
Han Kwang-sung
North Korean People's Army
The Recon bureau found traces
of Jang Myung-jun in Hanoi, Vietnam.
But there was a wrinkle.
They used fake passports
to fly into South Korea.
Pardon?
During the great famine,
our party produced meth
at the 915 research lab
to gain foreign currency.
But the party reversed the decision
for diplomatic reasons.
But having tasted money,
Jang disappeared
with a $1 billion Swiss account.
That much money could fill
the bellies of our entire country.
Why South Korea?
It means the money handler is there.
The head of 915, Kim Cheol-su.
If Jang and Kim are both caught
by the U.S,
The peace treaty talk is over
and the famine will continue.
The meeting venue has changed
from Singapore to Seoul.
It has been settled with the
South, so go right away.
I will come down myself in
a week with the delegation.
Find the money man
until then,
and get Jang and the $1 billion.
Release the samples.
And bring out the junkies.
Capitalism sure is nice!
You were alive.
I was surprised
to hear the rumor of your arrest.
Mr. Cho,
you must have been worried about me.
I was wondering if you were the one
who ratted me out.
That is impossible.
Right, you don't have
the balls to do that.
What is the status of the money?
As I have told you before,
pulling out of the investment
could result in heavy losses.
If you give me a bit more time...
Your girl sure is pretty.
If my daughter was alive,
she would be about her age.
Have you ever eaten
pickled human flesh?
It is not good at all.
Don't force me to make you taste it.
You got 3 days.
Use the red...
to add a shadow here.
Be thorough with the mascara.
Like this, slowly.
All done!
We tried out Oriental smokey make-up
that is all the rage
in Berlin club scene.
How do you like it?
Trendsetting Min-young's
Make-over Show.
That is it for today.
Subscribe and like are love.
What was that for?
How many times did I
call you for breakfast?
Come out!
I have to re-shoot it because of you.
I have to always beg.
Can't you see that I am working?
Powdering your face is working?
This is all you do after sending you
to the make-up school?
Like, like, love!
You are so clueless about it,
but a hot YouTuber
could make over $100,000 a month.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
So? How much have you made?
$36.
In a day?
No, I only started making some,
I made that in a year.
- Screw you!
- In a year?
Not a month, but a year?
So, $36 in 365 days
equals 10 cents a day.
Call your aunt "10-cent
girl" from now on.
You have got to put me down too?
I went places as a teen.
Really?
- I lost my appetite.
- Don't eat.
What is with you again?
You said you won't eat.
You have to take it away?
This food is wasted on you.
Why are you playing with
toys during work hours?
Don't say that, the world has changed.
This can search for missing people
and crack down on traffic violations.
Even if the world has changed,
investigations are done on foot,
and arrests are made by cops.
Come on, sir.
You are in Cyber Bureau now,
you should earn some certifications.
Do you think I will rot here?
I am going back to Major
Crimes even if it kills me.
Is the rumor true?
What?
That you closed a big case
with a North Korean cop.
- You heard that?
- Yes.
- You too?
No one can keep secrets around here!
My goodness!
Supernote plates had the potential
to collapse the world economy.
The North Korean cop was
named Lim Cheol-ryung,
and he said it had to be me,
he followed me around and relied on me.
That is all I will say.
I wish we could work
on a big case like that.
If you are a cop,
you will get a chance...
Why are they here?
Hey!
Cheol-ryung? Don't lie to me.
I am serious!
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
They are coming down for
the North Korea-US meeting,
and they have some bullshit pretense.
The Feds didn't believe
that they are coming down
for a drug dealer.
So?
They were going to assign
a volunteer as Lim's partner.
Okay.
None, not one volunteered.
Why not?
The rumor of your family
almost getting killed got around.
Everyone is trying to stay away.
So, no one seems to be registering
for Harvard?
Right, you will get it automatically.
Then you guys do it,
why are you asking me?
I got a wedding date.
All of sudden?
And you?
My kid is studying for college...
He is the one taking the exam, not you!
Will you stay in the
Cyber Bureau forever?
You should return to Major Crimes.
I have to!
What a headache.
If my wife finds out, she will kill me.
What? Cheol-ryung?
Him again? Why?
Well, it is for a simple
mission to catch a perp.
Did you forget that our
family almost died?
How could I forget that?
Then what is with you?
No way, not again.
You nuts?
I am not the only cop in Korea.
Right, so right.
If your brain had wrinkles,
you would never do it again.
Who is he after this time?
- Well...
- Is he...
coming to get me?
Forgetting me
would have been harder than dying.
Are you serious?
There she goes again.
He said we would meet again.
He said that out of courtesy,
as in "See you after unification."
Because he can't hold back that long.
I can't hold back because of you.
Don't you know men
don't care about anything
when they are in love?
She sure lives a sheltered life.
She will live a long life.
I have got no time to lose.
Did Cheol-ryung say he will meet you?
Oh man...
If he ever calls you,
just ignore him.
All right.
If you get mixed up in it,
it is an express divorce, got it?
All right, all right.
His secret hiding place
must be here somewhere.
Where is it?
This looks a bit off.
Be here...
See? Really?
No wonder this air purifier
never worked all that well.
Hey, what's up?
I floated the idea to my wife,
she flips out whenever
Cheol-ryung is mentioned.
Saying it is a divorce, it
is understandable though.
Just promise me one thing,
that I will return to Major Crimes.
I should be risking my
life to catch criminals,
not deceive my wife...
Holy cow...
- Jin-tae.
- Why are you here?
You will lie to my sister
with Cheol-ryung?
That is incredible...
- No way!
- Sis!
Of course not!
Want some money?
You can have $360.
That is like 10-year worth
of YouTube earning.
Then how much?
20 years? 30 years?
50 years? How much is that?
$1,800.
That is my spending
money for an entire year!
Sis!
Shush, I got it.
- Another condition.
- What is it?
Let me meet Cheol-ryung
before he leaves.
He has his own preferences,
I can't force him.
- Okay.
- Got it?
I will do my best.
- You promised.
- Okay!
In exchange...
Got it.
Inter-Korean Transit Office
Wow, so dreamy!
Are you the only cop down here?
Yeah, I am the only one.
So good to see you.
Eh? No gun?
The first rule of joint detail,
South Korean cop keeps the gun.
It is all automatic now.
There is a second rule.
Not using illegal weapons.
Don't use rolls of toilet
paper to beat perps up.
Very well.
I am actually hungry,
could we eat before we start?
Look at you,
I thought the case always came first.
Let me use the South tax money
to plump up my skinny body.
You don't look skinny at all.
- How about an eel?
- Very good.
Okay!
Word-of-Mouth Eel
This is so juicy, it is revolutionary.
Why do you use
"revolutionary" for everything?
Then what should I say?
Down here...
if you want to emphasize something,
you have got to add "freaking".
For example, it is freaking
hot, freaking cool.
You try it.
How juicy is it?
It is so freaking juicy.
You are so freaking good!
What is the mission this time?
Should I wiretap or hack?
Or I could pretend to investigate
and keep him running in circles.
Whatever you want...
Investigate by the book.
What?
Investigate the joint detail properly.
And dig for intel doing it.
He probably didn't come
here for a drug dealer.
They are up to something.
Honestly, what is it this time?
You can't be here
for one drug dealer.
That was freaking delicious.
What did he say?
I can't... Raise the volume.
Yes, sir.
My gosh, so embarrassing.
Let's start the investigation.
No need to hurry.
Take it slow.
Are you two agents?
- No...
- Yes.
- Yes!
- No.
These punks are distributing
a new type of drugs for a secret fund.
Okay, what else?
That is all there is to it?
I was told that one must
investigate on foot.
That is the old days, it
is all about science now.
Do you guys have the
concept of forensic science?
I guess all your intellectuals
are too busy making missiles.
You guys may have the concept.
Then do you have a way?
There is a revolutionary method.
Jong-gu, the guy in the picture I sent,
I need to find guys who deal with him.
Show us what Korean engineers can do.
Yes, boss. I confirmed the picture.
Here we go!
Looking for a new type of drug.
A proof picture of a drug sample.
A New Taste Red Flavor
Delivered in 30 min
Red pill.
Bait them.
Okay.
Sir, I am tossing in the bait.
I would like to buy the red pill.
I want to buy the red drug.
Anyone biting?
They can deliver
within 30 minutes on a motorcycle.
- Ask for a proof picture.
- Will do.
Could I see a picture?
Not that I don't trust you.
Sir, we got a biter!
Okay, yes!
Nice!
Forensic science.
We are after a suspicious motorcycle
that is circling the area.
Understand? Good luck!
Wait, there!
Could you zoom in?
Anguk building, western
flower bed, a plastic bag
Okay, suspect found,
Anguk Building, western garden!
Okay!
Hey, here it is!
Where are you going?
What is the holdout,
we have got to go after him!
When they run, we fly,
and when they fly, we use our wits.
Don't worry, there are security
cameras everywhere.
Checked.
I am worried.
That you might get hurt?
No.
That they might get hurt.
I will go easy on them.
Okay.
Excuse me!
I heard this is a joint
that sells the best dope in town.
Who is the head honcho here?
You?
This isn't a mom-and-pop shop,
everyone just walks in.
Popular joints are always so rude.
Kneel, idiots.
Buddy, on your knees.
Get down on your knees, morons!
You are a pig?
You got crap for manners.
How could you call me that
even before getting acquainted?
Go easy,
I can't bribe every damn pig in town.
It is just you two?
If you do not comply with the arrest,
I have the right to defend myself.
What are you saying?
I am genuinely curious,
do you have full medical coverage?
What a load of crap!
Boys!
Jeez, so many were in hiding.
So, isn't it better to walk away?
You may go.
Leave, leave, go, you idiot.
Go away, you dumb idiot.
Look at this punk, go home!
Damn, he caught it!
Bash them up!
Look at these idiots.
Cheol-ryung, you are free to
use weapons for 5 minutes.
1 minute is enough.
Yeah?
Don't move, idiot!
Yeah, I am a pig, you idiot.
You will cripple him.
Look who is talking.
Where did you get this drug?
Never seen them before,
they just left these samples.
He sounded like a Korean-Chinese.
He must be desperate for money,
he is unloading them very cheaply.
He is not some Costco sampler,
Sir, try this dope,
and just walked off?
Please!
I was going to unload
these and be done with it.
You should learn to lie properly.
What is this?
This is enough to lock you away
until you plaster the wall with crap.
No need to save up for retirement.
Sir! What is the point
of squeezing a hustler?
I will cooperate with
you to get those guys,
so please let us go this time!
How will you cooperate?
Those guys will be here
shortly to collect the money.
When?
Them?
Hey, guys.
Oh my...
Did you bring the goods as promised?
What happened to your face?
Oh, this?
South Korean police, don't move!
Lim Cheol-ryung?
Why are you here?
Should not you be dead?
Where is Jang?
Jong-gu!
We got a fallen suspect,
send me an ambulance!
What is the verdict?
Probably a concussion,
he will wake up in the morning
due to sedative.
Det. Lim!
You are causing trouble
as soon as you get here?
Are you a RoboCop or something?
The perp was in front of us,
should we have let him go?
Don't talk back at your superior!
I have had it, come with me.
- For what?
- Get over here!
What is it?
Cheol-ryung is uncontrollable,
- only I can manage...
- I know, I know.
Good work, really.
You caught the guy on
Interpol's Red Notice.
And 3kg of drugs were confiscated.
That is enough to fill our
team's quota for a year.
Yeah?
I am sensing something fishy,
have you uncovered anything from Lim?
A 17 versus 1 brawl
you see in movies took place in Seoul.
Hey, hey. Min-young.
Isn't that Cheol-ryung? Look at it.
That looks like Cheol-ryung.
Oh gosh, Cheol-ryung, Cheol-ryung!
He started swinging
as soon as he got here.
How is that possible?
Same thing as last time.
How is he still so hot?
See? That is why I told him
not to get mixed up with Cheol-ryung.
I wonder which Korean cop
is getting his butt kicked instead.
Wait a minute!
Not again!
I took these discreetly,
a burner phone and a passport.
Good, you did well.
I will work on these,
take Cheol-ryung home, feed him
and get him drunk like last time.
Are you nuts? My wife will kill me!
Okay, answer, answer, go on.
You see?
Hi, honey.
You got a death wish?
Get home with Lim right away!
I don't know where Cheol-ryung is!
Did you forget that our
family nearly died?
So why are you getting involved?
I didn't want to get involved.
I said no over and over again,
but Cheol-ryung said it had to be me.
When did I...
So-yeon.
But Cheol-ryung still
saved us last time.
Yeah, mom,
we should be thanking
him for saving us.
- Long time no see.
- It has been a while...
But this is all wrong!
He is here to catch a few drug dealers,
he won't shoot anyone
up like last time.
So don't worry, right, Cheol-ryung?
That is right.
- So-yeon...
- Mom.
Cheol-ryung, we have
a nice home, right?
Yes, it is very nice.
It looks like ours,
but it is not, the same
thing with the car too.
My home isn't mine either.
The party owns everything.
Right, a similar concept,
the bank owns everything.
So, until we pay them back,
my husband has to stay alive.
Am I a machine that makes money?
If you were, you would be
making decent money!
Men have to be handsome
like Cheol-ryung before anything.
Goodness...
I look very common, I
am not handsome at all.
Do you call that a common face?
Buddy, what about me then?
He is talking rubbish!
What a load of nonsense.
Kneel properly.
That is enough, wash up, and let's eat.
Yeah?
Should we order some Chinese?
Common face in the North
Why did you blame me?
Sorry, bud.
I missed working in the field,
I just had to.
Even so, one must separate
business and pleasure.
That is why I threw
the supernote plates
into the ocean,
and never got my promotion...
Must you rehash that
over and over again?
So, please help me get some promotion.
Let's be frank with each other.
Why is Jang so infamous
that he is on Interpol's Red Notice?
He has been in and out of
the country to smuggle meth,
and once it became difficult,
he moved to North America,
and started making and
selling a new type of meth.
A new type?
It is special because it can be made
with common chemicals.
But why did he enter South Korea?
He could go anywhere.
- That is...
- Go on.
That is what I am curious about.
Did you retrieve any
evidence from that guy?
A cell phone or personal belongings?
Not a damn thing.
I will go get some more beer.
We ran out,
I will go buy some, so chill here.
Gwang-yong was caught by the police.
What about it?
Lim Cheol-ryung was with them.
Lim Cheol-ryung?
The party must be desperate.
Bang!
Jang's henchman caught,
interrogation tomorrow.
Wrap it up before the
meeting, you must hurry.
This is plain wrong.
What do you mean?
Out of sight, out of mind!
I finally got over you,
how could you come back?
You came back for me, right?
Work was just an excuse.
No, I really came for work.
Liar!
What?
Why can't you look me in the eye?
Well, because I am sorry.
For what?
As you know,
it is realistically impossible.
But why do you decide that?
Why give up even before trying?
Then...
you could try unifying our countries.
There won't be any problems.
How could I unify...
Dang it!
What a nonsense.
How could I...
Jang looked like a
big shot in the States.
Why did someone like him come here?
Curious, right?
I asked that too.
What did Cheol-ryung say?
He is curious too.
It is your job to find out, you idiot!
I am not a calculator
that gives you answers,
just give me some time.
One second.
Holy cow!
Did he notice?
Damn it, got something
stuck between my teeth.
Got it, got it.
What is with that suit?
Why is he such an idiot?
He is younger than I am and
pats me on the shoulder.
I almost punched him in the jaw.
I think he was a golden parachute,
but because of the supernotes,
he missed a promotion.
Was that my fault?
It is his own incompetence.
His incompetence is a bottomless well.
All right, I have got to go.
If it was not for the wiretap,
I would have messed him up.
Sure.
- We must unify!
- Hey, get up!
What is going on?
What is with her?
- Will you get up?
- What is going on?
Snap out of it, you idiot!
Did she get drunk?
I am being patriotic with my face.
Do I have to unify our countries too?
It is about time,
she was quiet for a while.
What am I supposed to do with her?
You can't, it is a habit.
If it is unified, there
is no problem, right?
Yeah, let's go.
- Let her be.
- I am so embarrassed.
Call the police.
No need, I am the cop.
10 cents a day.
Bad drunk
Pork belly in the morning?
No one said we can't.
With what money?
Did you give her allowance again?
I don't even have a cent to my name.
Cheol-ryung, I cooked
this, so have plenty.
Koreans get their
strength from this food.
- No need.
- Here.
Just try it.
You have got to run out of
money, so you can panhandle.
I am making money, what
is wrong with YouTube?
Mom!
Come eat.
Did you see the piggy bank on my desk?
- Look around.
- It is not there.
I saved that to buy
the new BangTan Boys album.
BangTan Boys?
South Korea has that too?
I was in Korean Boys' Union.
He found a sense of humor.
Where did it go?
Look for it properly.
You little thief.
It was you, wasn't it?
Hey, stop that.
Can't we have a quiet morning?
I am so sick of this,
I should run away from home.
So early in the morning?
Yes?
Okay, I got it.
The suspect woke up.
Let's move.
No time to eat, there is no time...
I told you it was not me.
- You are the thief?
- Let's move!
Good morning, let us through.
Interrogation is in process,
please head back.
What do you mean?
This is now a Foreign Affairs case,
you are off the case.
What do you...
Hey, who are you?
Why are you...
Do you know him?
Thank you for your cooperation.
This fool is now mine.
You scum.
You know how to speak
Korean, you lied to me?
Did you ask? You certainly didn't.
My mom is Korean.
Get that paper out of my face.
I caught him, I will interrogate him.
Is it kind of like deja vu?
I have seen this situation before.
Whose fault was it that we lost Jang,
why are you causing a scene here?
Is that my fault?
How did they know
the route in New York?
Insisting that I leaked it?
How could I trust a nuke-making commie?
You are the one hoarding nukes,
and we can't make any?
He is my suspect now.
You won't find anything,
I will bet everything I own.
Didn't you say everything you own
belongs to the party?
- Brother!
- Hey!
I don't know what is going
on between you two,
but let's talk this out.
Hey! Hello, hello, excuse me.
Nice to meet you, I am
a Korean... detective.
Yup.
Nice to meet you.
What are you, a hobbit?
- What?
- Are you Antman?
Did you ask me if I am Antman?
You are starting off on the wrong foot.
Have you seen me before?
When did you see, how...
This is so frustrating.
Jin-tae!
Keep your underlings
on a tighter leash!
I'm sorry.
Det. Kang, let's go out,
Cheol-ryung, follow me.
Let's go, Cheol-ryung, come out!
Get over here.
South Koreans picked him up yesterday.
That means Jang is there too.
What is this?
And the North Korean
detective is back in the South.
These guys know each other?
Looks like.
We think they are in on it together,
that he is the one who gave
them the transport route.
Son of a bitch.
Listen, Jack.
This son of a bitch
killed one of our own.
He has to stand trial here in the U.S.
Get yourself on a plane to Seoul.
You got it.
How could I stop the
FBI from barging in?
FBI got involved?
This means that there
is something even bigger
than the supernote,
we have to find out first.
We have got to have a lead to do that.
Did you pull anything
from the burner I gave you?
The burner is being recovered,
but I looked into the passport,
there are only a few people
who could clone even the holograms.
Look, even the holograms are perfect.
I am the only one in
Asia who can pull this off.
- Sergei!
- Yeah, Sergei.
It means he sold the passport
and the burner to Jang.
- Yeah.
- So right.
The U.S. got involved.
Whereabouts of the money?
No evidence yet,
will bait the South and get help.
The thing about us Koreans is,
when the invaders barged in,
we became one to ward them off.
We can't let FBI bozos beat us
to the punch.
Are you hiding anything from me?
Jang may have brought in an expert
to produce the drug.
An expert?
Why are you telling me this now?
It is just speculation.
There is no way they smuggled
in such a large shipment.
Right.
If they set up a drug factory,
what about the chemicals?
There was a chemical theft a week ago.
Let me see.
What is Benzyl cyanide?
It is normally a cosmetic ingredient,
but it can also be used to make meth.
A guard died from broken neck.
That is them.
A stolen truck from there
was last seen on Yongin highway.
- Yongin?
- Yes.
Making that much meth will let off
a ton of poisonous gas and stench.
Jong-gu.
Get me a list of derelict factories
and warehouses
outside residential areas.
Let's head out to Yongin.
Hey, hey, just you two?
- Oh-deuk!
- Yes, sir?
Bring that and come with us.
Yes, sir!
They are going to execute you.
Cooperate.
You won't see your family anymore.
Don't get any families to see.
Yep.
I have shaken off the
North Korean detective.
Any info from the suspect?
He is not talking yet,
but I threw some bait,
so we will see what happens.
Sir, I have narrowed down the list
to about 300 suspected sites.
That is still too many.
Is anything over 500m
from the residential area?
Yeah, do that.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
Attaboy!
He walked past this sector.
All right, game on, let's go!
Eagle, you have the baton.
This is Eagle, I can see the target.
What? FBI deployed?
Okay, got it.
That idiot must have a lead,
too bad for your savings.
Brother.
Do you see anything?
The drone battery is almost dead,
and it is clocking out time.
Should we pull out?
Oh-deuk, man, just keep flying!
Don't make excuses.
Wait a minute.
Isn't that the stolen truck?
Get closer over there, a bit more.
Let's check it out before the sun sets.
You are sure, right?
I will void our first
rule for a moment,
take this.
- Oh-deuk.
- Yes, sir?
Stay here
and if we don't come
back in 10 minutes...
Should I go home?
- Call for backup, moron!
- Sure!
Let's move.
Why is an ambulance here?
Captain!
These guys are dangerous,
keep your eyes open.
Be ready to fire.
Let's go.
Restricted Number
Did you like the hospital food?
Captain, I got out of
there, where are you?
Comrade Gwang-yong,
you have a long tail.
You know we don't allow the hostage.
Clean up the mess.
Thank you for your dedication.
Freeze! Show me your hands!
Hey! Hey, hey!
There is a bomb! Boom!
What are you doing here?
It was an honor to serve you.
I will carry out your order.
Back! Back!
Are you okay?
You are it, you are the spy.
How did they know?
It is all my fault?
Your incompetence screwed us
every time.
What are you doing? Get off of him!
What's with you two?
It is a damn show here,
what are you doing in my country?
Do you not see that?
Come with me.
Come on!
Briquette BBQ
Let's disinfect.
Cheol-ryung, listen carefully.
Jack, listen carefully too.
It is a state of emergency.
Greatest American, North
and South Korean detectives are here.
Others might laugh
at me for saying this,
but we are the Avengers.
Thanos is about to snap his finger,
should Iron Man and Captain America
have a pissing contest?
Cool your pride!
Let's have an
international joint detail!
If you are keeping
secrets, let them all out.
All will be forgiven!
This clown knows shit.
You're a fucking liar.
Jack, your entire team is hospitalized,
who will you work with?
And you, Cheol-ryung,
all your leads are gone!
Who exactly is Jang?
What is that?
Do you two know each other?
I told you he was a liar.
He was a superior I respected,
but not anymore.
He was a guerrilla
dispatched to Africa,
and his men are all mercs.
You only talk when I beg
to spill everything, right?
You said all will be forgiven.
All right, all right.
So why did he bring in the mercs?
Money.
Money?
2 months ago,
I received an e-mail
from an alias 'Adolf Bormann'.
That is how I was able to get Jang.
I believe that Bormann is
a Korean-American named Michael Cho.
Michael Cho is
laundering it, he is uh...
- Money laundering?
- Laundering.
If Cho backstabbed Jang,
it means he took the money.
So Jang brought in mercs
to get the money back?
Bingo.
Why did he choose South Korea?
Why else? It means the
money handler is there.
How much are we talking about?
The amount is not the issue.
He must be stopped before
he causes an even bigger mess,
but no leads.
I actually have something to spill too.
I confiscated the
suspect's burner phone.
- That is...
- Listen first.
I know who gave him the burner,
his name is Sergei.
If we catch Sergei,
we can get Jang's number,
and triangulate his current position.
Got it?
Okay, okay, let's drink.
Drink this and we are
on a 3-way joint detail.
- Very well.
- Okay.
I love this!
Let me tell you something
from my childhood.
There was a show
called 'Chief Inspector'.
The protagonist was an
actor named Choi Bul-am.
With a trench coat and
a cigarette in his mouth,
he looked so cool!
Back then, he looked so old,
but now I am his age,
it is too cruel!
Jin-tae, stop being a cheap drunk.
How could you be so curt?
Use honorific words.
Say 'hyung' to him.
I don't know what honorific words mean.
No such thing in English.
We are all friends.
Wait, what is your birth year?
I was born in 1982.
Let's do it the American way.
Hey! Hey!
I am older right?
I think the other one looks better.
Yeah?
Do you like him that much?
Yeah, I always see him
in slow motion.
Was it like that when
you first saw Jin-tae?
Don't know, I don't remember.
Dad is almost home.
What? No!
- Yeah?
- No, no, no!
- That was fast.
Could you clean up here?
Oh man...
Bring them!
What are you doing?
You are holding it upside down.
Okay, go away.
Cheol-ryung, are you hurt?
It is okay.
Come, sit over here.
Let me see you.
How are you?
Fine, thank you, and you?
Better now.
What happened to your face?
We had a group of volunteer work.
This is Jack,
he is an FBI agent.
My wife and daughter, sister.
Nice meeting you.
Good evening.
So good to meet you.
You speak Korean so well.
I heard Korea was full of beauty,
it really is true.
Look at you, I thought you didn't know
how to use honorifics.
I think you should wash up.
You should.
- Oh yeah, little.
- Give him dad's big clothes.
- Son of a gun.
- Shower, shower.
- Washroom.
- It is over there.
Show him where it is, honey?
Don't have any, I threw them away.
No! Where is it?
The one with the striped T-shirt!
It is okay, she was too much anyway.
She is not the only woman on earth.
It is okay.
Come on...
Okay.
I gave up some intel just to give them
the impression that I am cooperating.
Good, watch yourself around
that South Korean detective though.
They play like they are enemies,
but they are on the same side.
The Americans know about the money.
It is all over if they
come sniffing around,
hurry up.
We must secure the money first.
And don't trust the
South Korean detective.
They talk about a single Korean race,
but they are in bed with Americans.
Understood, sir.
I think they both clued in.
What about Det. Kang?
Well, you know what he is like.
It is me we are talking about,
I used booze to knock out them.
I am so damn sober,
while Cheol-ryung and
Jack are drunk as a bat.
These guys are more
careless than they look.
By the way, do I get reimbursed
for the extra expenses?
I better get every single cent back.
The expenditure isn't the problem,
just stay alert.
You're the South Korean rep.
Oh yeah, there is a guy
named Michael Cho,
could you look him up?
Michael Cho?
He may have stolen Jang's money.
So, Jang must have smuggled
in to get his money back,
with his henchmen.
Got it, got it, Michael Cho.
Oh my, oh my!
Please change into this.
- Okay.
- Change.
What is it?
All right, that is it
for now, I have to go.
Hey, Jin-tae...
Idiot, he hung up on me.
- Is that a scar?
- Scar? Where?
That must have been
painful, it is so big.
- Oh this?
- Let me see.
I got hurt
while fighting off the Russian mafia.
- Russian mafia?
- That sounds so surreal.
On the back too, it is so big!
Came up to me when I was in Moscow,
he came up behind me, and just...
You are so incredible.
Stop showing off wounds
from the playground.
Back home, even disinfectant is rare
so we just use bean paste on it.
That is nothing at all? You
are so hot, Cheol-ryung.
You can't call that a scar.
I was about to cuff a cow thief,
I sensed something behind me.
I turned back
and see a bull breathing heavily.
He charged at me, then bam!
Why did the bull do that?
I am serious, I got a
scar here to prove it!
I never lie!
- Stop it.
- Don't do that.
How about this?
Have you ever defused a bomb?
- Bomb?
- Oh my god.
I worked for 3 years in
the bomb disposal unit.
- You were not scared?
- Not at all.
Hey, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack!
I defused one in college
on a group blind date.
I defused it
and still live with her.
My wife, the bomb!
So funny, huh?
Hey, hey.
Freaking hot
Have a great meal.
You are so sweet, thank you.
Thank you.
I need something for the hangover...
Cheol-ryung, would
you like some coffee?
No need.
Why do you even
drink that bitter thing?
Thank you.
You too.
Is your eye messed up?
Don't flirt with her.
I scoured social media
and found a lead on Sergei.
This is a former Russian
model named Natasha.
She is presumed to
be Sergei's girlfriend.
We will stake out near her place,
you guys look into Michael Cho.
Let's move.
We will cover Cho.
Will Sergei show up in the next 3 days?
We have to hope for that.
We seriously need a wire in there.
Why doesn't she ever leave?
Oh my...
How did you know we were here?
I asked Capt. Pyo.
You are so devoted.
It is good, it is really good.
Look, she is leaving.
Does she have to leave
when we are eating?
I am going to go plant the wire,
she can't be left alone,
could someone tail her?
I will follow her.
You will stand out too much.
Then I will go!
You will stand out even more!
Then I will go with Cheol-ryung.
We can pretend to be a couple.
Couple?
Yeah, do that, but fool around.
Good, Jack, you watch the fort here.
- I am heading out.
- Be careful!
Nice!
Hurry up.
This is so exciting,
is all policework this thrilling?
Isn't my acting amazing?
I think I am built for this.
Isn't it weird
that she is buying in pairs?
No way...
Look out! Look out!
You again?
I wondered where you were,
you were hiding here?
Nice.
I don't know, I really don't!
How could you not?
You sold a burner to Jang.
Let's wrap it up quickly,
give me the number.
Excuse me! Call me a lawyer!
Korea isn't some global pushover,
why did we use our tax money
to lawyer up a Russian?
That is why I settled here.
If I was in Russia,
I would be tortured
and sent to Siberia.
Human rights here are the best!
I could really send you to Siberia.
I knew this would come up,
so I requested a letter of cooperation.
You know it is only a 2-hour flight
from Vladivostok.
Scared?
Buddy.
Vladivostok?
2 hours?
Russian officials are lazy as hell.
Do you know that sloth from Zootopia?
S-e-r-g-e-i...
Call me right now.
Why does he want me to
call him to the other room?
Yeah, Det. Seo, what is it?
You wanted me to call you.
What? Already at the airport?
What airport?
He will come straight here?
Tell him to get some
rest before coming over.
What the heck are you talking about?
Does he want to take this idiot back
to Vladivostok tomorrow?
He should check out
the traditional village,
Gwangjang Market,
and get some tasty gimbap
while he is in town.
All right, then let him come.
Straight as an arrow.
Buddy.
I feel so bad for your
pretty girlfriend,
Natasha.
Stubborn idiot.
What was that about a Russian cop?
We got 3 countries represented,
and Russia should be too.
Jack, you said you fought
off the Russian mafia, right?
You are...
No.
- Oh, yes.
- No. No.
- Yes.
- No no no no no.
Yes.
No.
This is insane.
I only know how to flirt
and swear in Russian.
That is more than enough.
We have to get Jang no matter what.
Okay.
Come on. Come on!
This is so freaking stupid.
It tears me apart
to send you to Siberia.
You know what happens
in the gulag sausage fest.
Tarkovsky!
Your eyes are so beautiful.
My eyes?
Let's have a good time tonight.
I ain't spending a night with you!
Pervert, get back!
Your daddy is a freaking beggar!
Where is the washroom?
Washroom!
Washroom! Washroom!
He is insane! Please!
Shut your mouth!
Hyung, hyung!
Don't call me that,
I need a reason to help you.
- 010!
- What?
- 6742!
- Buddy, input it here.
Begin.
Must we go this far?
Is your heart getting soft?
It is not that...
But there are innocent people...
Was your family killed
because they were criminals?
We must get our revenge.
Of course.
North Korean delegation has arrived
through the Panmunjom today.
The 2-day trip will be attended by
Central Military Commissioner
Kim Jung-taek,
and is expected to make a big leap
in the ongoing negotiation.
Head home now.
I will.
Got a location ping of the burner!
He is in a vehicle, heading
toward Youngdong Bridge.
Where are they going?
I got a list of calls
made with the burner!
Jang and his men visited a club
owned by Cho a few days ago.
It is called Chroma.
Oh, Chroma.
Jang visited Michael Cho?
- Okay, got it.
- Hey, Jin-tae.
We got no warrant or evidence,
if things go south, we are done!
Do I look like an idiot?
I will go in posing as a clubber,
and arrest him if I see him.
Jin-tae, you have never been to a club?
VIPs get private rooms,
so they won't be on the floor.
- Yeah?
- Yup.
So what can we do without a warrant?
We can't do it right now!
There is one way to do
it without a warrant.
What?
I was a club junkie...
I mean, as an experienced clubber,
here is what happens inside.
Men from VIP rooms will ask me
to join them.
I frequented all those rooms back
in my heyday.
What then?
I am a walking search warrant!
I am going to take a look.
Be careful.
If there is a problem,
I will get to you like a bullet.
Like a bullet?
A bit slower than a bullet...
Okay.
Time to execute that warrant.
Yes, hottie confirmed.
Good evening!
South Korea sure is fancy,
so many are here today.
Got a company dinner?
What is so funny?
I have been thinking.
$1 billion is stored in here,
and it is all mine
if I just kill one guy.
What are you getting it?
So why the heck are you pulling out
when the business is good?
You are just a fugitive,
you can't even use this.
$5 million is enough
to live off somewhere
in the Philippines.
And I will send you the
living expenses too.
Think of it as returning
to a farming life.
I admire your guts, very well.
I will give it a thought
over a drink, yeah?
Bring out the Arman de Brignac set.
Arrived in Seoul,
what is the situation?
Waiting in ambush,
hunt initiating soon.
Lose South, American
cops, return at once.
Excuse me for a second.
- What is it?
- Jin-tae.
Cheol-ryung is hiding
something from us.
Hiding what?
Jang's money, the drug
money, it is $1 billion.
He came to get that.
$1 billion?
Why are you telling me this now?
He wants Jang and the money.
Then we will be left empty-handed.
Listen.
I am going after Jang.
You go after the money.
What is going on...
How much is $1 billion in Korean won?
1 trillion won?
You idiot!
We are short-staffed as is,
you are fooling around out here?
Get back to the kitchen!
The boss' VIP came,
bring the Arman set to the penthouse.
My apologies, sir.
Boss' VIP, got it.
Hello?
Captain.
I found out what the North is after.
What is it?
I was not going to care
if you took some crumbs.
But you don't know your place yet.
It is not about knowing my place,
but reading the room.
Do I still look like your minion?!
I have got to at least taste
the expensive booze.
Please don't kill me...
Money is like drugs.
Once you get a taste, you
only stop when you are dead.
I feel terrible for your daughter.
Stop, please stop, comrade Jang.
We got the money, please stop this.
You are a backstabbing idiot!
Did you think I would not know
you tipped off the FBI?
We pushed too far,
let's stop before...
Damn it...
Min-young
Jang is in the penthouse!
Min-young, please head home.
Jack.
Why? Hey!
Hey!
I am sorry.
Hey! Goddamn it.
I...
I am... Adolf Bormann...
Have to stop...
the massacre...
Let's go.
Get going! Hurry up!
Move in! On the double!
Cheol-ryung.
There he goes.
What are you doing?
Hyung, I am sorry.
Hey! Lim Cheol-ryung!
Don't fucking move!
I am DPRK Social Security's
Lt. Lim Cheol-ryung!
I request an escort to
the North's delegation!
We got played again!
See? I told you he was up to something!
But you could not find out why
and end up in this mess?
I found it, but you got here too late.
It is $1 billion!
You and I will be kicked to the curve!
Why should I?
I was following my orders.
Then take the responsibility
and get back the $1 billion!
Sir! Sir!
We found Jang's vehicle
near Pyeongtaek port.
He may be trying to smuggle into China.
Let's go, we are wasting time.
We will clean up your mess,
so fly home tomorrow.
Det. Kang, go rest up at home.
I will make sure you
rest for good this time.
This is all I get for risking my life?
Is that it?
I will follow you to Pyeongtaek, sir!
Stop getting in the way,
and go retrieve the
wiretaps at Kang's home.
Wiretaps?
Did you think we just trust you?
Are you naive or something?
No wonder you got backstabbed
by Lim Cheol-ryung twice!
I have had it.
What?
How dare you say that?
North Korean Delegation Hotel
Good work, what about Kim Cheol-su?
He is dead, sir.
All of the party's threats
are now eliminated.
Good to see you.
Comrade Lim Cheol-ryung
wrapped up this case.
Is that so? Good work.
The Swiss bank security key?
You are the true hero of our party.
I promise you a huge reward.
The German chemist who created
poisonous gas used on Jews...
I am... Adolf Bormann...
Have to stop...
the massacre...
Lim Cheol-ryung
The US-North Korea meeting ended
without a resolution today
after stating each other's stances.
North's representative Kim Jung-taek
criticized the U.S. for
coming to the table
without any offers.
Lim Cheol-ryung
The North delegation will return...
What do you want?
Your informant was Kim Cheol-su.
He said a massacre needs
to be stopped before he died.
His alias Bormann was
a Nazi chemist officer
who massacred Jews...
This could be bad.
It is too late.
I am going home.
I am home.
You are a bit late.
Hey, Jack.
Is your flight heading out soon?
Yes. Hey, listen.
There is something I need
you to check for me first.
Something the informant
said before he died.
Who cares what Kim Cheol-su said?
It is over now.
How did you know his name?
I mean, lucky guess, I guess.
Jack?
Traitor-ass motherfucker.
Oh, shit.
I am incredibly honored!
The almighty comrade Kim Jung-taek
came here to catch a nobody.
Your damn mouth is
still alive and kicking.
I believed your word
that our people can be saved
by bringing in dollars,
and I tossed the soldier's honor
to peddle drugs,
but that money went into
just one idiot's mouth.
You should have just
stuck to your orders.
You clued in too quickly.
My boss was the traitor.
Jang Myung-jun knew everything,
every move we made.
So, why was he caught?
- Caught on purpose?
- Yes!
And those guys are
targeting Jin-tae's family.
I will save his family,
you go after Jang.
Is he training a mutt or something?
Hey, hey hey.
You know me, right?
What? Yes.
Hey, rookie.
Would you like to
cooperate with the FBI?
Really?
Mom, I am so scared...
Don't worry.
Dad will come to
save us like last time.
It is okay, don't cry.
May I check your ID?
Seoul Metro Police, Kang Jin-tae.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good.
Could we get some food?
Food?
No, we don't want to eat.
We're all doing this
so that we don't starve.
- Hey!
- What's with you?
Could you at least order us Chinese?
Are you able to eat right now?
We collected a ton of coupons.
We did that so we can
order sweet and sour pork!
I want to use them all before I die!
Our corpses will look better.
- I want double portion!
- Hey!
Double portion?
- Please don't mind her...
- I want double!
- I have to have it!
- No, don't listen to her.
Is she out of her mind?
Pick something!
Shut the heck up!
- Please forgive her...
- Now.
She inhaled a lot of
carbon monoxide as a kid...
Anyone home?
I came with an important message.
You can kill me,
but please let my family go.
Shut up. You will see them soon.
I came with an important message.
Jack came to rescue us!
Min-young, watch out!
Min-young, open the
door! Open the door!
Hurry!
Good job.
Thank you.
The main server is under control.
What is it?
You idiot!
Jacked in, shutting off elevators.
- Honey!
- Sweetie!
You okay?
Yeah, I am fine.
We are okay too, Jack rescued us.
Don't worry about us.
Good...
Under Maintenance
Dammit!
Ready to transfer, sir.
Move all $1 billion to my account.
Yes, sir.
They are connected, initiating a hack.
- What is wrong?
- We are being hacked.
What is this?
Money is being taken
out of the account.
You moron, then stop them!
Right away, sir.
Freaking idiot!
You must enter the tiger's den
to catch the tiger.
Do you know how long I prepped
to get you outside the country?
Take it all, I don't need it.
Then why did you kill
my innocent family?
Isn't it a husband and a father's duty
to go to hell and back to seek revenge?
Listen, Myung-jun.
What are you planning?
And what about the poison?
5 minutes after pressing this,
poisonous gas will be released
from the roof of this building.
Any living beings within
a 3km radius will perish.
Isn't it a brilliant plan?
And this is for the fallen comrades...
Hyung.
I am sorry about yesterday.
Shut it, our detail isn't over.
They are trying to
release poisonous gas.
He is a stereotypical villain.
Cover me.
What?
Okay, got it.
Hey, Lim Cheol-ryung!
Idiot...
Enough! You are finished!
You have crossed 2 lines
you should not have.
First, you entered
South Korean territory.
Second,
you messed with my family.
So what, you weak as heck.
Cheol-ryung! Are you okay?
Where is the bomb?
- It is over there!
- Okay!
Will you kill innocent people?
How are they innocent?
My daughter and wife were burned alive.
If the South allowed asylum,
they would not have died.
South Koreans should taste
what hell is like as well.
Jack!
Look, it is a poisonous gas bomb.
What do you mean?
Poison!
Honey, we are almost there...
You can't come here...
I don't believe it, Jack, what do I do?
I got less than 3 minutes.
If I don't defuse it,
we are all dead.
Why are you asking me that?
You said you were in
the bomb disposal unit!
Oh my god! It was a long...
I know, I know, it was a long time ago.
Can't you help? Please?
- Wait, wait...
- What do we do!
Hole, that hole.
Deactivation key, key!
Key?
There is a key there, you
have got to find the key.
Right, key!
I see it, I see it!
Dammit!
- You can't go in there!
- Hold on!
- They are Jin-tae's family.
- Hello, there.
- Captain!
- Why are you here?
Jin-tae is up there right now.
There is a bomb on the roof!
Hey, hey, this is an emergency.
Cheol-ryung!
Key!
We have got to find a key
that deactivates the bomb!
Give me the key.
I will finally get
to see my daughter and wife.
Lim Cheol-ryung.
It would be best if
we don't meet again.
No!
Radio them.
Look!
Get the key.
Closer!
- One second, sir.
- A bit more!
Now!
Cheol-ryung!
Hyung, by the way...
are we okay to go home?
Your wife will kill us.
We can just kneel!
Hey, Jack!
Hyung, are you okay?
I am okay, thank you so much.
Did you just call me 'hyung'?
I said "Huh? Are you okay?"
Not 'hyung', I said,
"Huh? Are you okay?"
He uses English only
when he is at a disadvantage.
What should I do with this?
If you take it,
do you think it will
really be used for food?
I got an idea.
What kind?
Wait and see.
Oh my god, I must have gone insane...
Min-young, I see it, I
see him in slow motion...
- Oh gosh...
- You see it?
I see it, that is incredible!
I don't believe it, honey!
- Dad!
- Honey, get over here!
Come here, you fool!
UNICEF has donated $1 billion
to help aid North Korea's
food shortage.
The donor and the source of donation
are receiving attention.
UNICEF has stated that as per request,
they won't identify the donor.
Hyung, I am sorry.
For what?
You didn't get the
promotion because of me.
I never wanted a promotion,
I am just glad I didn't get fired.
It was a really good idea.
And I have to keep on living like this.
Be well.
Take care.
Cheol-ryung, I will wait for you.
Will you wait?
Yes, I will wait.
Jeez...
Min-young, have you been to the States?
Never.
Would you like to join
me when I head back?
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Look.
Why is he coming back?
Hey!
Don't flirt with her.
Oh gosh...
For me?
- Oh gosh...
- So cool.
Jeez...
Thank you, Cheol-ryung.
I will wait for you!
Cheol-ryung!
Oh my god!
You finally won him over.
Don't touch it.
Congrats, congrats!